That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
The Ameld River
Episode 4: In the Kingdom of the Dwarves
Rimuru and his friends follow
the Ameld River north
（リムル）
リムルたちは
アメルド大河に沿って北上していた
in search of artisans who can make
clothing and houses for the Goblins.
ゴブリンたちの家や服を作るための
技術者を探しに
They're heading to Dwargon,
the Kingdom of the Dwarves.
ドワーフの王国 ドワルゴンへ
行くのである
He's accompanied by Rigur
and two other Goblins,
同行者はリグルと ほか２名
and Gobta, who says he's been to
Dwargon before, is their guide.
そして 一度ドワルゴンに
行ったことがあるという
ゴブタが道案内である
The Tempest Wolves that
evolved from the Direwolves
牙狼族(がろうぞく)からテンペストウルフに
進化したオオカミたちの
run as fast as the wind.
移動速度は風のように速い
Hey, no need to push yourself too hard.
（リムル）
おい
あんまり無理はしなくていいぞ
Yes, Master!
（リムル）あ… ひゃあ〜！
Why are you going even faster?!
（リムル）
なぜ加速する〜！
（ゴブタ）ハア ハア…
（リムル）リグル君
Rigur-kun, who gave your brother his name?
君のお兄さんは
誰に名前 付けてもらったの？
Sir! I'm told he received his name from
a passing Demon called Lord Gelmud.
（リグル）
はっ！　兄は通りすがりの魔族の
ゲルミュッド様に
付けてもらったそうです
He saw promise in him.
見どころがあるからと
（リムル）ゲル…
Gel...?
“ゲルミュッド”
魔王軍の幹部です
Gelmud. He's an officer
in the Demon Lord's army.
Oh...
（リムル）ほお…
Wait, Demon Lord's army?!
ていうか 魔王軍？
魔王がいるのか
There's a Demon Lord?
ヴェルドラは
勇者もいるって言ってたし…
Veldora said there was a hero, too...
I hope I never end up meeting them.
Sounds like nothing but trouble.
大変そうだから 関わり合いに
ならないようにしなくっちゃな
Hey, Ranga...
（リムル）
なあ ランガ
Master?
I killed your father, which means
you should want revenge, right?
（リムル）
俺って お前の親父(おやじ)さんの
敵(かたき)ってことになるよね？
Don't you think about that at all?
その辺 気にしなくていいの？
I've been wondering about that all along...
（リムル）
前から気になってたんだけど…
I do think about it.
（ランガ）思うところはあります
But, Master, you not only spared
us after defeating us in battle,
しかし 我が主(あるじ)は
戦いに負けた我々を
許したのみならず
you also gave us a new name.
名前まで授けてくだされました
I have only gratitude toward
you, and no resentment at all.
感謝こそすれども
恨むようなことはありません！
Our loyalty belongs to you
and you alone, Master.
我らの忠義は
我が主 ただお一人のもの
でございます！
Gobta.
（リムル）ゴブタ
（ゴブタ）は… はい！
Yes, sir?
What is the town we're heading for like?
（リムル）
俺たちが向かってる町は
どんな所なんだ？
W-Well...
え… ええっとっすね
It's officially called the
"Armed Nation of Dwargon."
正式には
武装国家ドワルゴンという名称っす
天然の大洞窟を改造した美しい都で
It's a beautiful city constructed
from a modified natural cave system,
and it's home to not only dwarves,
but elves, humans, and lots more.
ドワーフだけじゃなくてエルフとか
人間もいっぱいいるっす！
Elves?!
（リムル）エルフ！
（エルフたち）ウフフ…
（リムル）
エルフか…
Elves, huh?
ドワーフ王のガゼル･ドワルゴは
英雄王と呼ばれる人物で
The dwarf king, Gazel Dwargo,
is known as the Hero King.
He's deeply admired by all the people.
国民に ものすごく慕われてるっす
Elves...
（リムル）エルフ…
エルフ〜
Great Rimuru?
（リグル）リムル様？
（リムル）
そ… そのドワルゴンって
I-Is it okay for monsters
like me to enter Dwargon?
俺みたいな魔物が入っても
大丈夫なのか？
No need to worry.
（リグル）心配いりません
Dwargon is a neutral free-trade city.
ドワルゴンは中立の自由貿易都市
All fighting is prohibited by the king.
あの地での争いは 王の名において
禁じられているのです
I see...
（リムル）ほう
それを可能とするのが
And that's made possible by the Armed Nation
of Dwargon's immense military might.
武装国家ドワルゴンの
強大な軍事力です
It's said that the dwarven army has
been undefeated for a thousand years.
この千年
ドワーフ軍は不敗を誇るのだとか
A thousand years?
（リムル）
千年！　そりゃあ すごい
That is impressive!
No one would be dumb enough to
get on that king's bad side.
（リムル）
そんな無敵の王を
敵に回すようなヤツはいないわな
Last time I went there, they picked
a fight with me outside the gate...
前に行ったときは門の前で
There won't be any trouble!
（ゴブタ）絡まれたっす…
（リグル）トラブルなんて
起こりませんよ
Hm?
（リムル）
なんか 今
I'm pretty sure a huge flag
just went up... Was it just me?
盛大にフラグが立ったような気が
しないでもないが…
Look, Great Rimuru!
（リグル）
あっ リムル様
いい感じに焼けてますよ
They've cooked up nicely!
It's said that it can take a Goblin two months
or more to walk to the Dwarven Kingdom.
（リムル）
ドワーフの王国へは
ゴブリンの足では 歩くと
２か月はかかるといわれている
The Canaat Mountains
With the help of Ranga and his packmates,
その距離を
ランガたちの頑張りのおかげで
リムルたちは
３日で走破したのだった
Rimuru's party traversed the same
distance in just three days.
The Armed Nation of Dwargon
So that's where the Elves...
（リムル）
あそこにエルフが…
じゃなくて！
I mean, the Dwarves are, huh?
ドワーフたちが
いるんだな
すてきなエルフに…
I hope some beautiful Elves...
I mean, some skilled Dwarves
are waiting there for us.
じゃなくて！
腕利きの職人に会えるといいな
（リグル）
本当にリムル様とゴブタだけで
行かれるのですか？
Are you sure you want to go in
with just Gobta, Great Rimuru?
Yeah.
We don't want to draw too much
attention by going in a big group.
あまり大勢で行って
目立たないほうがいいだろう
I'll take Gobta along to show me the way.
ゴブタは案内役で連れていく
But...
しかし…
大丈夫っすよ！
We'll be fine!
Master...
（ランガ）我が主…
Don't worry.
（リムル）心配いらない！
We'll be back soon, so wait for us here.
じゃあ 行ってくるから
ここで待っているように
（リグル）お気をつけて
Please be careful.
This is quite a line.
（リムル）すごい行列だなあ
They must be strict about checking everyone.
チェックも厳しそうだ
中に入れば
自由に行動できるんっすけどね
Once we're inside, we can move
around as we please, though.
As we please, huh?
（リムル）自由か…
Hey! Hey, hey, hey!
（男Ａ）お〜い おいおいおい！
（男Ａ）
魔物が こんな所にいるぜ？
What's a couple of monsters doing here?
We're not inside yet, so we
can still kill it, right?
（男Ｂ）
まだ 中じゃねえし
ここなら殺してもいいんじゃね？
And there it is! We're already in trouble!
（リムル）
はい 早速 絡まれました！
フラグ回収です
Flag collected!
Hey, Gobta-kun, did you hear something?
（リムル）
おいおい ゴブタ君
なんか聞こえないかね？
Yes, I did...
はい 聞こえるっすね…
前 来たときも ここで
ボコボコにされったす
I was beat up here last time
I tried to get in, too.
It's the fate of us weak monsters.
弱い魔物の宿命みたいなもん
なんすよ
（リムル）
宿命ねえ…
Fate, huh?
おい 雑魚い魔物！
こっち 無視してんじゃねえよ！
Hey, weakling monster! Don't you ignore us!
ていうか
しゃべるスライムってレアじゃね？
Wait, isn't a talking slime pretty rare?
I bet we could make a fortune off of it!
見せ物として売れるんじゃね？
Gobta-kun.
（リムル）ゴブタ君
（ゴブタ）え…
Do you remember our first rule?
（リムル）
ルールその１を
覚えているかね？
Of course, sir!
はい！　もちろんっす！
ルールその１
人間を襲わない！
Rule one: no attacking humans!
All right, now, close your
eyes and cover your ears.
（リムル）
では 少し目をつぶり
耳を塞いでおくんだ
Huh?
Don't look this way, whatever you do.
（リムル）
決して こっちを
見てはいけない！
Got it!
了解っす！
Now, then...
（リムル）さてと…
Hey, there.
（リムル）
おいおい！
俺は寛大だから 今なら許してやる
I'm a generous sort, so I'll
spare you if you leave now.
Get out of here.
さっさと うせな！
You're just a puny, little weakling
monster! Don't you mess with us!
クソ雑魚の
魔物のくせしやがって
ナメてんじゃねえぞ！
お前 死んだぞ！
You're dead now!
I was gonna let you live,
but you've pissed us off!
殺さずにいてやろうと
思っていたんだがな
俺たちを怒らせた以上
そうはいかんぞ！
（リムル）
おっ 雑魚っぽいセリフ
Ah, that's something a weakling would say.
A puny, little weakling monster?
（リムル）
クソ雑魚の魔物？
それは俺のことか？
Are you referring to me?
Who else would we be referring to?!
（男Ａ）
てめえに決まってるだろうが！
Oh! Do I look like a slime to you?
（リムル）
ほ〜う
俺がスライムに見えるのか？
Well, I am one, but anyway...
（リムル）
まっ そうなんだけど
（リムル）クックック
How long have you had the
mistaken idea that I'm a slime?
いつから
俺がスライムだと勘違いしていた？
Allow me to show you my true form!
見せてやろう この俺の真の姿を！
Huh?
Huh? Did my Mimic skill evolve?
（リムル）
なんか“擬態”が進化してる？
（男Ａ）
ヘッ どうせ見た目だけだろ
You just changed your appearance!
Did you think you could
scare us off with that?!
（男Ｂ）
それでビビって
逃げるとでも思ったか！
Just run away already, damn it.
（リムル）
もう… 逃げてくれよ めんどくせえ
Good grief...
All right, fine!
もういいや　かかってこい！
Come at me!
ヘッ 死にやがれ！
Now you die!
お前らも やれ！
You guys get him, too!
Companions C.D.E appeared.
There are more of them!
（リムル）
仲間 増えた！
Take this!
くらえ！
Slash Attack!
斬撃(ざんげき)！
Heavy Hitting Cut!
Fireball!
（男Ｄ）ファイヤーボール！
Magic Wall!
（男Ｅ）マジックウォール！
I-Impossible!
（男Ｃ）バ… バカな！
My Fireball...
（男Ｄ）俺のファイヤーボールが…
His fur is so tough...
（男Ｅ）なんて硬い毛だ！
Did you guys just do something?
（リムル）今 何かしたのか？
（リムル）
おおう… やられちゃうかと思った
Yikes! I thought they were gonna kill me!
Mimicry is amazing!
“擬態”スゲえ
Now it's my turn.
（リムル）俺のターンだな？
（男たち）あっ…
— Menace —
Er...
Crap.
ヤッベ…
Results of Menace to follow.
（大賢者(だいけんじゃ)）
“威圧”の効果を報告します
Report
16 fled.
16 fled
68 became confused.
Report
16 fled, 68 confused
92 fainted.
Report
16 fled, 68 confused, 92 fainted
34 soiled themselves.
失禁34名…
Thanks, but I don't need a damage report!
（リムル）
いや 被害報告とか いいから…
Hey!
（カイドウ）こら〜！
（リムル）あっ！
You there!
（カイドウ）そこの お前〜！
Huh?
A slime?
スライム？
Tee-hee!
（リムル）てへぺろ！
Some guide you turned out to be.
（リムル）
なにが案内役だ この野郎
And you've got some nerve to be sleeping now.
ていうか こんなときに ずぶといな
Well?
（カイドウ）で？
（リムル）あっ はい！
Uh, right!
Actually... that's all.
（リムル）
でも… 以上っす
Captain of Security  Kaido
（カイドウ）ふむ…
Well, since you're a slime and a goblin,
they probably saw you as easy targets.
まあ スライムとゴブリンだから
絶好のカモだと思われたんだろうな
I was only trying to
scare them off, really...
（リムル）
ちょっと追い払おうと
思っただけだったんですが
I'm very sorry for all the trouble!
ご迷惑をおかけして
本当に すんませんっした！
Well, what you've said agrees
with witness reports.
（カイドウ）
まあ 大体 目撃者の証言と一致する
Just this once, I'll let you two—
今回は君たちを…
Captain! We've got trouble!
（兵士）隊長！　大変だ！
There's an Armorsaurus in the mine!
鉱山にアーマーサウルスが！
（カイドウ）
なんだと！　討伐隊は？
What?! Where's the suppression force?
（兵士）既に向かいました！
They're already en route,
but Garm and his brothers were deep
in the mine gathering magic ore,
それより 魔鉱石の採掘に
奥まで潜ってたガムルたちが
大ケガを…
and they were badly hurt!
Do we have potions?
（カイドウ）回復薬は？
Not enough. We've allotted most
of them to war preparations.
それが 戦争の準備だかで
足りてないんですよ！
あいつらは 俺の
兄弟みたいなもんなんだ
Those guys are like brothers to me!
W-We can't waste time!
Start looking for potions!
と… とにかく 回復薬を探せ！
（リムル）旦那
Sir...
（カイドウ）
なんとしても かき集めろ！
Gather all you can, whatever it takes!
Sir.
（リムル）旦那
（カイドウ）ん？
Huh?
あっ！
なに勝手に出てきてんだ お前！
How dare you leave your cell?!
Now, now, this isn't the time for that, is it?
（リムル）
まあまあ
それどころじゃないんでしょ？
あれ…
Look.
You need that, don't you?
必要なんじゃないですかね？
What's that?
これは…
Healing potion. The best around!
You can drink it or apply it directly!
（リムル）回復薬ですよ
飲んで良し かけて良しの
優れものですよ！
Huh?
ふむ…
Why not give it a try?
（リムル）
とりあえず試してみちゃどうです？
うむ
（兵士）
隊長！
魔物の言うことを信じるんですか？
Captain! You're going to
trust the word of a monster?
We don't have time!
（カイドウ）時間がない！
Let's go!
（カイドウ）行くぞ！
（兵士）は… はい カイドウ隊長！
Yes, Captain Kaido!
You'd better stay in your cell!
お前 ちゃんと牢(ろう)に入ってろよ！
He was really worried about his subordinates.
（リムル）
あんなに部下の心配をして…
He seems like a good guy.
いいヤツのようだな
Skill
A cradle!
（リムル）揺りかご！
A diamond!
ダイヤモンド
Actually Not
A hand drum!
鼓(つづみ)
Just Killing Time
A boat!
船！
And now...
からの…
Tokyo Tower!
東京タワー！
Just Killing Time
This guy sure is a deep sleeper.
（リムル）それにしても こいつ
Rather, Punishing Gobta
ホントに よく寝るな…
You saved them. I thank you.
（カイドウ）
助かった　ありがとう！
I heard you gave us that potion! Thank you!
（ガルム）
あんたが薬をくれたんだってな！
ありがとよ
Don't mention it.
My arm was nearly ripped off.
（ドルド）
腕がちぎれかけてて 生き残れても
仕事がなくなるとこだった
Even if I'd survived, I would've lost my job.
ありがとう
Thank you!
You're very welcome.
（リムル）
どういたしまして
なんか言えよ！
Say something!
Really, thanks so much!
（ガルム）ホントに ありがとよ！
We owe you!
（ドルド）恩に着るぜ！
Am I free?
（リムル）釈放っすか
Naturally.
もちろんだ
I've never seen such
remarkable potion before.
（カイドウ）
それにしても
あんなすごい薬は初めて見たぜ
礼と言っちゃなんだが
It won't be enough to thank you,
but if you ever need anything, just ask me.
俺にできることなら
何でも言ってくれ
In that case...
（リムル）それなら…
I see.
（カイドウ）なるほど
そういうことなら
腕のいい鍛冶師を紹介しよう
In that case, I'll introduce
you to a skilled blacksmith.
I'd appreciate that.
（リムル）それは助かります！
No need for thanks! Just leave it to me!
（カイドウ）
礼なぞ不要だ　任せとけ！
Welcome!
（女）いらっしゃい
I can tell I'm in dwarven country!
さすがはドワーフの国
It looks so much more civilized
than the Goblin Village.
ゴブリンの村に比べて
随分 文明的だ！
This way.
（カイドウ）こっちだ
（リムル）あ…
Don't get lost, now.
（カイドウ）迷子になるなよ
Wow!
（リムル）
スゲえ！
あの装飾 細工が細けえ…
Such detailed workmanship!
What's up with that sword?
Is it actually shining?!
何だ あの剣？
うっすら光ってる？
Is it magic?
魔力か？
Yeah, that right there.
It's the guy who made that.
ああ あれあれ
あれを作ったヤツだよ
（カイドウ）これから会う鍛冶師
The blacksmith we're about to meet.
（リムル）ほう！
This is the place. I guarantee
his skills are top-notch!
（カイドウ）
ここだ　腕は保証するぜ
Hey, Bro, you here?
おい！　兄貴 いるかい？
Bro?
（リムル）兄貴？
Hey, Kaido. Give me a sec.
（カイジン）
カイドウか 少し待ってくれ
Sure.
Forgive us for interrupting.
（リムル）おじゃましま〜す
（カイドウ）カイジン
That's my older brother, Kaijin.
俺の兄貴だ
Weaponsmith  Kaijin
Wow... He definitely seems like
the tough-as-nails workman type.
（リムル）
おお
頑固一徹の職人って感じ
（カイジン）あ？　スライム？
A slime?
お前たち 知り合いか？
Friend of yours, boys?
カイジンさん
このスライムですよ
Kaijin, this is the slime we told you about.
Three Dwarf Brothers
Youngest Brother
Myrd
Middle Brother
Dord
Oldest Brother
Garm
昨日 大ケガした
俺たちを
The one that saved us when
we were hurt yesterday.
助けてくれたのは！
Oh, so this is the one!
（カイジン）
おお そうだったのか！
You have my thanks.
ありがとう 感謝する
Oh, really, it was nothing...
or maybe it was?
それほどでもあるような
ないような？
So, what can I do for you?
（カイジン）それで 何の用で？
ふむ… なるほど
I see.
話は分かった
I get what you're saying.
But I'm sorry... I'm pretty
backed up at the moment.
だが すまん！
今 ちょっと立て込んでてな
Thanks to the impossible order a
certain numskull minister put in...
どこぞのバカ大臣が
むちゃな注文をしてきてなあ
Impossible order?
（リムル）むちゃな注文？
We might be going to war soon,
so he asked for twenty longswords...
戦争があるかもしれないって
ロングソードを20本
今週中に作れってな…
by the end of the week, no less.
I'm short on materials,
so I've only made one so far.
まだ１本しか出来てないんだよ
材料がなくって
Then, couldn't you have told him
it wasn't possible and refused?
だったら 無理だと言って
断ったらいいじゃねえか
（リムル）
もっともだ
Good point.
Don't be dumb!
バカ野郎！
I did tell him that, at first!
俺だって“無理だ”って
最初に言ったんだよ
But then that damned Minister Vesta said...
そしたら
クソ大臣のベスターのヤツが…
My, my!
Minister Vesta
The great Kaijin that everyone
calls the best blacksmith around
王国でも名高い鍛冶師の
カイジン様ともあろう
お人が
can't handle such a simple task?
この程度の仕事も
できないのですかな？
なんぞと ほざきやがったんだよ
He had the nerve to say that!
Could you have let that slide?!
許せるか？　あのクソ野郎が！
That bastard!
My boss was like that, too...
（リムル）
部長も そんな感じだったな
I guess interpersonal relationships
are a pain in any world.
どこの世界も
人間関係は めんどくさいんだな
You say you're short on materials?
（リムル）材料がないって？
Yeah, I need a special ore called magic ore.
（カイジン）
ああ 魔鉱石という特殊な鉱石が
必要でな
We were trying to dig some up yesterday...
（ガルム）
昨日
俺たちが堀りに行ったんだが…
...but that Armorsaurus showed up.
（ドルド）
アーマーサウルスが出てな
（リムル）なるほど
I see.
But that mine was pretty
well cleared out, anyway.
どちらにせよ あの鉱山は
ほとんど掘り尽してて…
There wasn't any ore left.
もう残ってないようだ
And even if I did have the materials,
（カイジン）
しかもな… たとえ材料があっても
20本打つのに
２週間はかかるんだよ
it takes two weeks to make twenty swords!
Yet I have to get them
to the king in five days.
なのに あと５日で
王に届けなければならない
They contracted smiths all over the kingdom
and allotted the work to all of us.
国で請け負い
各職人に割り当てが行われた仕事だ
If I can't do it, my certification
as a smith could be revoked.
できなければ
職人の資格の剥奪もありえる
兄貴…
Bro...
That really sucks.
（リムル）困ったもんだな
（リムル）
あれ？
Wait...
Magic Ore
Magic ore? Don't I...
魔鉱石って 俺…
持ってるんじゃね？
Magic Ore
have some of that?!
（リムル）フッフッフ〜
ハ〜ハッハッハ！
ハッハッハッハ…
Old man...
親父…
Can you use that?
これ 使えるかい？
Wait...
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait!
That's magic ore!
魔鉱石じゃねえか！
And it's unbelievably pure!
しかも 純度が
ありえんほど高いぞ！
Hey, old man, are you blind?
（リムル）
おいおい 親父
あんたの目は節穴かい？
Huh?!
It's not even magic ore!
魔鉱石じゃない！
It's already been processed!
It's a cluster of magisteel!
既に加工された
〝魔鉱塊(まこうかい)〞だ！
Magisteel Cluster
（リムル）正解
Precisely!
I can make even stronger swords with this!
更に強力な剣を作ることができる！
It can't be...
そんな… この塊 全てが？
This entire cluster is...
こ… これは譲ってくれるのか？
Y-You're sure I can have this?
あっ もちろん
金は言い値で払うぞ！
I'll pay you handsomely, of course!
Well, now... I wonder what I should do...
（リムル）
さて どうしたもんかね〜
（リムルの口笛）
（カイジン）くう〜 何が望みだ？
What is it you want?
I'll do anything in my power for it!
（カイジン）
できることなら何でもする！
（リムル）その言葉が聞きたかった
That's what I wanted to hear.
（リムル）
誰か親父さんの知り合いで
I'd like you to find some fellow artisans
who'll come to my village to teach
their crafts to the villagers.
技術指導として村まで来てくれる
人がいないか探してほしい
That's all you want?
そんなことでいいのか？
Our priority right now is the "shelter and
clothing" part of food, shelter, and clothing.
（リムル）
俺たちにとって最優先が
衣食住の“衣”と“住”なんだよ
I'd also like to get some clothing for
future use, as well as weapons and armor.
まあ それと 今後の衣類の調達や
武具なんかも頼みたい
フッ お安いご用だ
That's easy!
だけど…
But...
今から剣を そろえようとしても…
Even if you start on those swords now...
Can you finish in time?
（リムル）間に合うのか？
Well, I'll do what I can.
まあ やるだけ やってみるさ
All right, let's get started!
さあ すぐ始めるぞ！
Right!
（ドルドとガルム）へい！
（ミルド）うんうん！
Oh, yeah.
（リムル）
そうだ…
大賢者さん ちょっとよろしい？
Great Sage-san, got a minute?
Yes.
（大賢者）
はい
Hey, old man...
（リムル）なあ 親父さん
You said you've already made one, right?
（リムル）
さっき １本作ったって言ってたな
その剣を見せてくれ
Can I see it?
Oh... Hey.
あ… おい
It's magnificent.
（リムル）これは見事だ
Even an untrained eye like mine
can tell you have real skill.
素人の俺にだって
親父さんの腕が確かなのは分かる
ん？　この剣も光って見えるな
The blade looks like it's shining.
（カイジン）
魔鋼(まこう)を芯に使ってるからな
It has a magisteel core.
Put simply, it's a sword that
matures in the image of its user.
（カイジン）
簡単に言うと
使用者のイメージに沿って
成長する剣ってわけだ
（リムル）スゲえ〜！
Amazing!
That's incredible! I wish he'd
come to the village himself!
（リムル）
スゲえな… この親父さんが
村に来てくんないかな〜
For that to happen...
っと そのためにはっと…
I'm gonna borrow this sword!
（リムル）
ちょっと その剣 借りるぞ
Hey!
（カイジン）お… おい！
The sword...
（ガルム）剣が…
（ドルド）何を？
What did you...
リムルの旦那？
Rimuru, you...
Just give me a second.
（リムル）少し待て
（リムル）
大賢者 解析しろ
Great Sage, analyze it.
（大賢者）
解析対象 ロングソード
Analyzing: Longsword.
Analysis successful.
成功しました
Use some magisteel clusters
to make some copies.
（リムル）
魔鉱塊を使って
コピーを作成してくれ
Producing copy.
Producing Copy
Successful.
（大賢者）
成功しました
Twenty longswords made
from magisteel clusters!
（リムル）
魔鉱塊のロングソード
20本 完成だ！
What?!
A party?
（リムル）お祝い？
Yeah! I made my delivery
on time, thanks to you!
（カイジン）
ああ！　おかげさまで
無事に納品が終わったんでな
But you don't have to do that for me.
（リムル）
別に そんなことしなくても
Aw, come on! There'll be lots
of cute elf girls there!
エルフのきれいなおねえちゃんが
いっぱいいるから！
（リムル）エルフ！
Elf?!
Yeah! It's a place called
"Butterflies of the Night"
（ドルド）
そそ！　“夜の蝶(ちょう)”って店でな
where girls of all ages, from young
to mature, wait on you hand and foot!
若い子から熟女まで！
紳士御用達の店なんだよ
Butterflies...
（リムル）蝶…
（ミルド）うんうん！
Speak, man!
（リムル）
しゃべれよ！
C'mon, Rimuru. It won't
be a party without you.
おいおい リムルの旦那が来ないと
始まらないぜ？
Yeah!
Well, if you insist, I suppose I'll have to.
（リムル）
まあ そこまで言うなら
しょうがないなあ
That's the spirit!
（ガルム）そうこなくっちゃ！
Sheesh...
（リムル）
まったく…
困ったヤツらだぜ！
What am I gonna do with you guys?
Butterflies
of the Night
Oh, Kaijin! How nice to see you!
（店のママ）
あら カイジンさん
いらっしゃ〜い！
Welcome!
（一同）いらっしゃいませ〜！
（リムル）
うっひょ〜！
Elves!
エルフ！
Eros...
エロフ…
I mean, elves!
もといエルフ！
（エルフＡ）うわ〜 かわいい！
Oh, how cute!
Oh, yesssss!
（リムル）
キター！
Hey! I had my eye on it first!
（エルフＢ）
ちょっと〜！
私が先に目ぇ付けてたのに
Oh, my God! Her dress is so thin!
（リムル）
ちょっ… ヤッベえ！
服 うっす〜い
It feels so nice and bouncy!
（エルフＣ）
ポヨヨンしてる
気持ちいい〜！
My thoughts exactly...
（リムル）
気持ちいいのは こっちです…
So this is what women's boobs feel like...
これが女の人の胸の感触…
I've never felt them before.
生まれて初めて
This must be paradise!
これが楽園か…
After the way you resisted coming here,
you sure seem to be enjoying yourself.
（カイジン）
嫌がってた割には
えらく楽しんでくれてるみたいだな
Huh?
N-No, I wouldn't say that.
い… いや それほどでも？
（リムル）くう〜！
（店のママ）
さあ 飲みましょう 飲みましょう！
Well, come on! Let's drink!
Yeah!
（一同）は〜い！
During this time, I was in heaven.
（リムル）
このとき 俺は天国にいた
I want to live in this valley forever.
ずっと この谷間で過ごしたい
What a blessed life,
so abundant in peaks and valleys!
なんという豊かな谷間のある人生…
But fun times never last long.
しかし
楽しいときは長くは続かない
That's just how life is.
それもまた人生
Next time, "Hero King, Gazel Dwargo."
（大賢者）
次回「英雄王ガゼル･ドワルゴ」
Hero King, Gazel Dwargo